irooc.com 2017-06-06

# privacy policy

At irooc, we are committed to protecting your privacy. Any information we collect, such as email addresses, is submitted at the visitors’ will. We do not and will not share any personal information with any third parties unless by governmental order. Other information is collected by our Payment Services provider but we have no access to this information. You may direct further inquiries to the Payment Services provider here:

PayPal.com:  
http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/privacy-outside

2checkout.com:  
http://www.2checkout.com

Cookies

Your browser offers so-called “cookies”, which – if you allow their use – store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of our sites. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features you like best. And when you re-visit our sites, cookies can enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. However, cookies tell us nothing about you personally.  
We may use cookies to:

::Save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our sites.

We do not use cookies to identify, monitor or track any personally identifiable information. Our cookies in and of themselves do not contain any personally identifiable information about you. We do not merge or associate our cookie information with any personally identifiable information obtained by us or from third parties. You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. For more information on how to modify your browser settings to block or filter cookies, see http://www.cookiecentral.com/faq/.

However, note that if you reject some or all cookies, your experience at our sites and on other sites throughout the World Wide Web may not be complete. Some sites require cookies to function, such as those with e-commerce features. In addition, if you do not allow cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of personalized content delivery offered by us or other Internet sites.  
Third Party Cookies At Our Sites

While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with the payment processes are placed by our Payment Services provider. We do not have access to these cookies or any information that they may contain; please contact the Payment Services provider for more information on these cookies.

PayPal.com:  
http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/privacy-outside

2checkout.com:  
http://www.2checkout.com

Registration Forms

Our site’s registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address).

Contact information from the registration forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary.  
External Links

This site contains links to other sites. irooc is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.  
Sending Emails to Our Members

Please note that we send all new members a verification email to verify password and username. By submitting your email to us when you create an account, your email will be added within our opt-in email contact list. Members will receive periodic emails with information such as newsletters, email promotions on products or services, or special deals, from irooc, as well as any companies affiliated with irooc as well. If you wish to stop receiving these emails, you can click on the unsubscribe link that’s included with every email or contact us directly.  
Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: privacy@irooc.com
